Guide to the Roy Lightner Collection of Antique Advertisements, 1871-2009 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Products and Services--Large Format, 1894-2009, (8 boxes)
  - Campbell's Soup, 1906-1975, (4 folders) (Box 11)
  - Canada Dry, 1930-1931 (Box 11)
  - Canadian National, 1946-1956 (Box 11)
  - Canadian Pacific, 1946-1958 (Box 11)
  - Cannon Towels, 1934-1961 (Box 11)
  - Capehart, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
  - Carnation Milk, 1931-1960 (Box 11)
  - Carrier, 1947-1968 (Box 11)
  - Carter's underwear, 1921-1930 (Box 11)
  - Cashmere Bouquet, 1900-1959 (Box 11)
  - Caterpillar, 1960, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Champion Spark Plug, 1937 (Box 11)
  - Cheney Silks, 1921 (Box 11)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1917-1945 (Box 11)
  - Chesterfield, 1927, 1944 (Box 11)
  - Chicken-of-the-Sea, 1960-1974 (Box 11)
  - Chickering Pianos, 1907 (Box 11)
  - Chris-Craft, 1946-1967 (Box 11)
  - Church & Dwight (Arm & Hammer), 1937 (Box 11)
  - Clicquot Club, 1919-1945 (Box 11)
  - Clorox, 1931-1939 (Box 11)
  - Cobb's Creek Whiskey, 1937 (Box 11)
  - Coca-Cola (includes Fanta, Sprite), 1930-1999, (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Colgate, 1901-1973 (Box 11)
  - Container Corporation of America, 1937-1969 (Box 11)
  - Corona Typewriter, 1930 (Box 11)
  - Coty, 1923-1930 (Box 11)
  - Crane, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Cream of Kentucky, 1937 (Box 11)
  - Cream of Wheat, 1899-1958 (Box 11)
  - Cream of Wheat Lil' Abner cartoons, 1940-1953 (Box 11)
  - Crest Toothpaste, 1956-1969 (Box 11)
  - Crisco, 1921-1965 (Box 11)
  - De Beers, 1949-1978 (Box 12)
  - Delco-Remy, 1937 (Box 12)
  - Del Monte, 1919-1973 (Box 12)
  - Djer Kiss, 1917-1929 (Box 12)
  - Dole Pineapple, 1928-1958 (Box 12)
  - Drano, 1930 (Box 12)
  - Dr. Pepper, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
  - Dromedary Dates, 1913, 1921 (Box 12)
  - Du Pont, 1919-1976, (3 folders) (Box 12)
  - Eastman Dillan, 1969 (Box 12)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1901-1971 (Box 12)
  - Eden Washer, 1920 (Box 12)
  - Edison Electrical Institute, 1961 (Box 12)
  - Elamis Stationery, 1922 (Box 12)
  - Electric utilities, 1945-1966 (Box 12)
  - Elgin Watch, 1915 (Box 12)
  - Epilepticide, 1910s (Box 12)
  - Equitable, 1934-1969 (Box 12)
  - Esterbrook Pens, 1944-1953 (Box 12)
  - Ethyl Corporation, 1952 (Box 12)
  - Eutectic/Castolin, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Eveready, 1924-1931 (Box 12)
  - Eversharp, 1922-1942 (Box 12)
  - Fairbanks (includes Fairy Soap), 1902-1924 (Box 12)
  - Feen-a-Mint, 1937 (Box 12)
  - Fels Naptha, 1924-1945 (Box 12)
  - Firestone, 1919-1970, (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - First Pennsylvania Bank, 1965-1973 (Box 12)
  - Fisk Tires, 1919 (Box 12)
  - Fleischmann's, 1921-1951 (Box 12)
  - Florsheim Shoes, 1953 (Box 12)
  - Forstman Wool, 1955 (Box 12)
  - Franco-American, 1934-1955 (Box 12)
  - French Line, 1949-1958 (Box 12)
  - Frigidaire, 1927-1959 (Box 12)
  - Gaby Suntan Lotion, 1942 (Box 13)
  - Gem Razors, 1944 (Box 13)
  - General Electric, 1917-1961, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - General Mills [Includes Betty Crocker, Gold Medal, Washburn-Crosby], 1910-1974, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - General Motors Electromotive Division, 1946-1949 (Box 13)
  - Gerber's, 1934-1937 (Box 13)
  - Gillette, 1917-1947 (Box 13)
  - Glenmore Distilleries (King's Ransom, Kentucky Tavern), 1955 (Box 13)
  - Goblin Soap (Cudahy), 1919 (Box 13)
  - Gold Dust, 1917-1931 (Box 13)
  - Goodyear, 1919-1970 (Box 13)
  - Hanes underwear, 1942-1952 (Box 13)
  - Hart Schaffner and Marx, 1915-1959 (Box 13)
  - Hellmann's (Best Foods), 1928-1969 (Box 13)
  - Hercules Powder, 1919 (Box 13)
  - Hires Root Beer, 1919-1955 (Box 13)
  - H.J. Heinz, 1901-1959 (Box 13)
  - Honeywell, 1968-1970 (Box 13)
  - Hoover, 1919-1956 (Box 13)
  - Hormel, 1930-1974 (Box 13)
  - Hunt's, 1952-1965 (Box 13)
  - Insurance Companies of North America, 1964-1965 (Box 13)
  - International Correspondence Schools, 1919-1920 (Box 13)
  - International Silver, 1930 (Box 13)
  - Ipana, 1930-1959 (Box 13)
  - Iver Johnson firearms, 1918-1919 (Box 13)
  - Ivory, 1910-1974, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - J.B. Williams, 1911-1920 (Box 13)
  - Jello, 1918-1972 (Box 13)
  - Johnnie Walker Scotch, 1958 (Box 13)
  - Johnson and Johnson, 1917-1959 (Box 13)
  - Karo, 1903-1972 (Box 14)
  - Kellogg's, 1906-1970 (Box 14)
  - Kelly Springfield, 1937-1947 (Box 14)
  - Kent, 1953 (Box 14)
  - Kleenex, 1926-1956, 1992 (Box 14)
  - Knox, 1919-1939 (Box 14)
  - Kohler, 1926 (Box 14)
  - Kotex, 1922-1950s (Box 14)
  - Kraft, 1924-1974 (Box 14)
  - Kroehler Furniture, 1930 (Box 14)
  - Lea & Perrins, 1918 (Box 14)
  - Lees Carpets, 1949 (Box 14)
  - Libbey-Owens-Ford, 1937 (Box 14)
  - Libby, 1917-1956 (Box 14)
  - Lifebuoy, 1903-1924 (Box 14)
  - Lifesavers, 1952-1959 (Box 14)
  - Listerine, 1922-1955 (Box 14)
  - Lucky Strike, 1951, 1953 (Box 14)
  - Lux, 1919-1954 (Box 14)
  - Lysol, 1938 (Box 14)
  - Maine Tourism, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Manon Lescaut, 1924-1920s (Box 15)
  - Masonite, 1951 (Box 15)
  - Max Factor, 1934 (Box 15)
  - Maxwell House, 1924-1954 (Box 15)
  - Mazola, 1921-1930 (Box 15)
  - McCallum Hosiery, 1924 (Box 15)
  - Mellin's Food, 1894 (Box 15)
  - Mennen, 1900-1924, 1951-1953 (Box 15)
  - Metropolitan Life, 1922-1960 (Box 15)
  - Michelin, 1919 (Box 15)
  - Milwaukee Railroad, 1946-1951 (Box 15)
  - Miller, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Minute Rice, 1954-1955, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Minute Tapioca, 1918-1939 (Box 15)
  - Mobil Oil, 1925-1957 (Box 15)
  - Montgomery Wards, 1921-1930, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Moore Business Forms, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Morton's Salt, 1923-1963 (Box 15)
  - Mum, 1919-1960 (Box 15)
  - Nabisco (includes Uneeda), 1903-1972 (Box 15)
  - National City Company, 1922 (Box 15)
  - National Dairy Producers, 1944 (Box 15)
  - National Fluid Milk Producers (Got Milk campaign), 1996-2009 (Box 15)
  - Nestlé, 1954-1955 (Box 15)
  - New England Life, 1957 (Box 15)
  - New Haven Railroad, 1946-1949 (Box 15)
  - New York Central, 1951-1952 (Box 15)
  - Nicholson File Co., 1943-1954 (Box 15)
  - Norfolk & Western, 1949-1964 (Box 15)
  - Northern Pacific, 1945-1955 (Box 15)
  - Northwestern Mutual, 1937 (Box 15)
  - N.W. Ayer & Son house advertisements, 1928 (Box 15)
  - Old Dutch Cleanser, 1903-1931 (Box 15)
  - Oxirane, 1971-1973 (Box 15)
  - Palmolive, 1917-1970 (Box 15)
  - Parke-Davis, 1930 (Box 15)
  - Parker Pen, 1918-1965 (Box 15)
  - Pearline, 1895-1919 (Box 15)
  - Pear's Soap, 1903-1919 (Box 15)
  - Penn Mutual, 1950 (Box 15)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1945-1946 (Box 15)
  - Pepsodent, 1917-1930 (Box 15)
  - Pet Milk, 1924-1934 (Box 15)
  - Pillsbury, 1917-1970 (Box 15)
  - Planter's Peanuts, 1919 (Box 15)
  - Plate Glass Manufacturers' Association, 1937 (Box 15)
  - Polaroid, 1949-1979 (Box 15)
  - Post/Postum (General Foods), 1921-1969 (Box 15)
  - Procter & Gamble, 1927 (Box 15)
  - Prudential, 1903-1970 (Box 15)
  - Pullman, 1942-1955 (Box 15)
  - Purolator, 1937 (Box 15)
  - Pyrex, 1916-1937 (Box 15)
  - Quaker Oats, 1914-1964 (Box 16)
  - Quaker Puffed Rice/Wheat, 1919-1937 (Box 16)
  - Quaker State Oil, 1937-1960 (Box 16)
  - Ralston-Purina, 1901-1954 (Box 16)
  - RCA Victor (includes Victor Talking Machines, Victrola, Radiola, Victor and Red Seal Records, Whirlpool), 1903-1961 (Box 16)
  - Red Heart Dog Food, 1952 (Box 16)
  - Regal Shoes, 1942 (Box 16)
  - Rinso, 1930-1939 (Box 16)
  - Rock Island Railroad, 1903-1957 (Box 16)
  - Royal (Baking Powder, Gelatin desserts), 1903-1939 (Box 16)
  - R.T. French, 1929-1959 (Box 16)
  - Sal Hepatica, 1937 (Box 16)
  - Santa Fe Railroad, 1917-1959 (Box 16)
  - S.C. Johnson & Sons, 1919-1958 (Box 16)
  - Scott Paper, 1925-1959 (Box 16)
  - Sealed Power, 1937 (Box 16)
  - Sealtest, 1952-1960 (Box 16)
  - Seargent's Dog Medicine, 1934, 1957 (Box 16)
  - Sears, Roebuck & Co., 1901 (Box 16)
  - Sheaffer Pens, 1914-1942 (Box 16)
  - Shell Oil, 1942 (Box 16)
  - Shredded Wheat, 1909-1952 (Box 16)
  - Simmons Mattresses, 1924-1970 (Box 16)
  - Simoniz Wax, 1937 (Box 16)
  - Singer Sewing Machine Co., 1928-1959 (Box 16)
  - Southern Pacific, 1908-1958 (Box 16)
  - Squibb, 1924-1945 (Box 16)
  - Steinway Pianos, 1907-1939 (Box 16)
  - Stewart-Warner, 1937 (Box 16)
  - Sunkist, 1919-1972 (Box 16)
  - Sunmaid/Sunsweet, 1919-1955 (Box 16)
  - Sunshine (Loose-Wiles Biscuit Co.), 1930-1968 (Box 16)
  - Swans Down, 1925-1961 (Box 16)
  - Swift and Co., 1919-1953 (Box 16)
  - Testimonial advertising, 1902-1979 (Box 17)
  - Texaco (includes Havoline), 1913-1977 (Box 17)
  - Time Magazine, circa 1937 (Box 17)
  - Times Mirror Magazine Network, 1976 (Box 17)
  - Traveler's Insurance, 1935-1959 (Box 17)
  - Underwood Foods, 1937-1959 (Box 17)
  - Underwood Sundstrand, 1937 (Box 17)
  - Union Pacific, 1926-1964 (Box 17)
  - United Airlines, 1942-1965 (Box 17)
  - United States Army Recruiting, 1971 (Box 17)
  - Univac, 1969 (Box 17)
  - USL Batteries, 1937 (Box 17)
  - V-8 Juice, 1942-1999 (Box 17)
  - Veedol Motor Oil, 1937 (Box 17)
  - Vivaudom perfume, 1924 (Box 17)
  - Wahl Pens, 1922 (Box 17)
  - Wanamaker, 1902 (Box 17)
  - Warren Telechron, 1932-1953 (Box 17)
  - Waterman Pens, 1919-1949 (Box 17)
  - Watkins Cocoanut Oil, 1917-1920 (Box 17)
  - Weber Pianos, 1908 (Box 17)
  - Welch's, 1925 (Box 17)
  - Wesson, 1963 (Box 17)
  - Western Bancorporation, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Westinghouse, 1924-1954 (Box 17)
  - Wheatena, 1934 (Box 17)
  - Willard's Batteries, 1937 (Box 17)
  - Wilson Bros. Leathers, 1941 (Box 17)
  - Woolfhead lingerie, 1918 (Box 17)
  - World War II effort, Electric Companies, 1942 (Box 17)
  - Wrigley's, 1928-1934 (Box 17)
  - Yardley, 1942-1952 (Box 17)
  - Zerone Antifreeze, 1937 (Box 17)
- Cars and Trucks--Small Format, 1899-2008, (9 boxes)
  - A.B.C., 1909 (Box 18)
  - Acme, 1922 (Box 18)
  - Acura, 1986-2008, (3 folders) (Box 18)
  - Aerocar, 1906 (Box 18)
  - American La France, 1904 (Box 18)
  - American, 1911 (Box 18)
  - American Motors, 1969-1992 (Box 18)
  - Apperson, 1919-1920 (Box 18)
  - Aston-Martin, 1989-2003 (Box 18)
  - Atlas, 1910 (Box 18)
  - Atterbury, 1918 (Box 18)
  - Audi, 1970-2000 (Box 18)
  - Austin, 1970-1974 (Box 18)
  - Autocar, 1904 (Box 18)
  - Avanti, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Babcock Electric, 1906 (Box 18)
  - Baker, 1908 (Box 18)
  - Bentley, 1987-2005 (Box 18)
  - Bertone, 1986 (Box 18)
  - BMW, 1971-2008, (4 folders) (Box 18)
  - Briscoe, 1919 (Box 18)
  - Brush, 1908 (Box 18)
  - Buick, 1925-2006, (9 folders) (Box 18)
  - Cadillac, 1902-1910, (1 of 8 folders) (Box 18)
  - Cadillac, 1922-2008, (2-8 of 8 folders) (Box 19)
  - Chalmers, 1911-1922 (Box 19)
  - Chandler, 1915-1929 (Box 19)
  - Checker, 1963-1968 (Box 19)
  - Chevrolet, 1920-1999, (1-7 of 11 folders) (Box 19)
  - Chevrolet, 2000-2008, (8-11 of 11 folders) (Box 20)
  - Chrysler, 1924-1999, (1-9 of 10 folders) (Box 20)
  - Chrysler, 2000-2003, (10 of 10 folders) (Box 21)
  - Citroen, 1956-1988 (Box 21)
  - Columbia, 1905-1923 (Box 21)
  - Corbin, 1910 (Box 21)
  - Crestmobile, 1904 (Box 21)
  - Crosley, 1948 (Box 21)
  - Croxton-Keeton, 1910 (Box 21)
  - Daewoo, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Daniels, 1922 (Box 21)
  - Datsun/Nissan, 1959-2004, (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - Denby, 1918-1920 (Box 21)
  - Detroit Electric, 1910-1920 (Box 21)
  - Dodge, 1915-2003, (10 folders) (Box 21)
  - Eagle, 1992-1996 (Box 22)
  - Elcar/Elkhart, 1920 (Box 22)
  - Elmore, 1908-1910 (Box 22)
  - Essex, 1920-1929 (Box 22)
  - Ferrari, 1986-1993 (Box 22)
  - Fiat, 1961-1988 (Box 22)
  - Fisher Body, 1927-1944 (Box 22)
  - Ford, 1927-1990s, (1-15 of 19 folders) (Box 22)
  - Ford, 2000-2003 (continued), (16-19 of 19 folders) (Box 23)
  - Franklin, 1904-1928, (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Frazer, 1948-1950 (Box 23)
  - Fredonia, 1904 (Box 23)
  - General Motors Corporation, 1918-2003, (3 folders) (Box 23)
  - General Motors Trucks, 1919-1920 (Box 23)
  - Glide, 1907 (Box 23)
  - GMC Trucks, 1960-2003, (4 folders) (Box 23)
  - Grabowsky, 1910 (Box 23)
  - Graham-Paige, 1927-1928 (Box 23)
  - Great Western, 1910 (Box 23)
  - Haynes, 1904-1910 (Box 23)
  - Hillman, 1951-1953 (Box 23)
  - Honda, 1973-2002, (5 folders) (Box 23)
  - Howard, 1910 (Box 23)
  - Hudson, 1910-1939 (Box 23)
  - Hummer, 2003 (Box 23)
  - Hupmobile, 1909-1923 (Box 23)
  - Hyundai, 1986-2001 (Box 24)
  - Infiniti, 1990-2003 (Box 24)
  - International Harvester (International Trucks), 1922-1995 (Box 24)
  - Isuzu, 1981-2001 (Box 24)
  - Jaguar, 1968-2003 (Box 24)
  - Jeep, 1950-2007, (3 folders) (Box 24)
  - Jewett, 1924 (Box 24)
  - Kelly, 1910 (Box 24)
  - Kia, 2001-2006 (Box 24)
  - King Midget, 1958-1960 (Box 24)
  - Knox, 1907 (Box 24)
  - La Fayette, 1918-1924 (Box 24)
  - Lancia, 1980-1988 (Box 24)
  - Land Rover/Range Rover, 1972-2001, (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - LaSalle, 1927-1931 (Box 24)
  - Lexus, 1989-2003 (Box 24)
  - Lincoln, 1920-1979, (1-7 of 11 folders) (Box 24)
  - Lincoln, 1980-2002, (8-11 of 11 folders) (Box 25)
  - Locomobile, 1908-1920, (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Lotus, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Mack, 1987 (Box 25)
  - Maja, 1908 (Box 25)
  - Marmon, 1912-1930, (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Maserati, 1982-2008 (Box 25)
  - Maxwell, 1919-1926 (Box 25)
  - Mazda, 1975-2003, (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Mercedes-Benz, 1905-2007, (4 folders) (Box 25)
  - Mercer, 1910 (Box 25)
  - Mercury, 1939-2003, (1-5 of 7 folders) (Box 25)
  - Mercury, 1939-2003, (6-7 of 7 folders) (Box 25)
  - Merkur, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Metropolitan, 1960 (Box 25)
  - Metz Plan Car, 1928 (Box 25)
  - MG, 1963-1978 (Box 25)
  - Mitchell, 1907-1920 (Box 25)
  - Mitsubishi, 1980-2003 (Box 25)
  - Moon, 1917 (Box 26)
  - Morris, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Motorette, 1901 (Box 26)
  - Nash, 1927-1954 (Box 26)
  - National, 1910 (Box 26)
  - Northern, 1905-1910 (Box 26)
  - Oakland, 1922-1931 (Box 26)
  - Oakland/Pontiac, 1931 (Box 26)
  - Oldsmobile, 1902-2002, (8 folders) (Box 26)
  - Opel, 1959-1989 (Box 26)
  - Overland, 1925-1931 (Box 26)
  - Owen, 1910 (Box 26)
  - Packard, 1906-1958, (4 folders) (Box 26)
  - Paige, 1915-1924 (Box 26)
  - Palmer-Singer, 1910 (Box 26)
  - Pathfinder, 1916 (Box 26)
  - Peerless, 1904-1928 (Box 26)
  - Peugeot, 1969-1989 (Box 26)
  - Pierce, 1903-1921 (Box 26)
  - Plymouth, 1933-1999, (8 folders) (Box 26)
  - Pontiac, 1948-1970s, (1-3 of 7 folders) (Box 26)
  - Pontiac, 1980s-2003, (4-7 of 7 folders) (Box 27)
  - Porsche, 1971-2002 (Box 27)
  - Pope, 1904-1908 (Box 27)
  - Premier, 1910 (Box 27)
  - Rambler, 1902-1965, (3 folders) (Box 27)
  - Rapid, 1908 (Box 27)
  - Rauch & Lang, 1909-1913 (Box 27)
  - Regal, 1910 (Box 27)
  - Renault, 1954-1988 (Box 27)
  - Reo, 1905-1931 (Box 27)
  - Republic, 1919 (Box 27)
  - Rolls Royce, 1979-1993 (Box 27)
  - Rover, 1961-1980 (Box 27)
  - Royal, 1906 (Box 27)
  - Saab, 1970-2003 (Box 27)
  - Saturn, 1990-2003, (2 folders) (Box 27)
  - Saxon, 1915-1917 (Box 27)
  - Scorpio, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Selden, 1919 (Box 27)
  - Service, 1919 (Box 27)
  - Simca, 1958-1960 (Box 27)
  - Simplo, 1908-1919 (Box 27)
  - Singer, 1927 (Box 27)
  - Stearns, 1910 (Box 27)
  - Stevens-Duryea, 1910-1912 (Box 27)
  - Studebaker, 1904-1963, (4 folders) (Box 27)
  - Stutz, 1926 (Box 27)
  - Subaru, 1976-2001 (Box 27)
  - Sunbeam, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Suzuki, 1983-2001 (Box 28)
  - Thompson, 1919 (Box 28)
  - Tickford, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Toyota, 1970-2003, (1-2 of 5 folders) (Box 28)
  - Toyota, 1970-2003 (continued), (3-5 of 5 folders) (Box 28)
  - Transport, 1922 (Box 28)
  - Triumph, 1927, 1958-1980, (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Volkswagen, 1958-2003, (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Volvo, 1959-2002 (Box 28)
  - Waverley, 1902-1912 (Box 28)
  - Wayne, 1905 (Box 28)
  - Whippet, 1928-1929 (Box 28)
  - White, 1906-1916 (Box 28)
  - Wilcox, 1909-1911 (Box 28)
  - Wills Sainte-Claire, 1922-1926 (Box 28)
  - Willis-Knight, 1920-1930, (2 folders) (Box 28)
  - Winnebago, 1985 (Box 28)
  - Winton, 1899-1922 (Box 28)
  - Yale, 1902-1904 (Box 28)
- Cars and Trucks--Large Format, 1906-2003, (7 boxes)
  - Acura, 2000 (Box 29)
  - American, 1912 (Box 29)
  - American Motors, 1954-1978 (Box 29)
  - Anglia (Ford), 1959 (Box 29)
  - Auburn, 1927 (Box 29)
  - Austin, 1948-1970 (Box 29)
  - Autocar, 1919-1945 (Box 29)
  - BMW, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Buick, 1916-1999, (6 folders) (Box 29)
  - Cadillac, 1914-1995, (5 folders) (Box 29)
  - Chandler, 1921-1924 (Box 29)
  - Chevrolet, 1920-1999, (7 folders) (Box 30)
  - Chrysler (includes De Soto and Imperial), 1925-2000, (8 folders) (Box 30)
  - Citroën, 1955 (Box 30)
  - Columbia, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Cortina (Ford), 1959-1969 (Box 30)
  - Datsun/Nissan, 1964-1999 (Box 31)
  - Delage/Du Pont/Maybach Zepellin, 1932 (Box 31)
  - Detroit Electric, 1913 (Box 31)
  - Dodge, 1920-2000, (6 folders) (Box 31)
  - Durant, 1930 (Box 31)
  - Essex, 1920-1931, (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Fiat, 1954-1984 (Box 31)
  - Fisher Body, 1925-1958 (Box 31)
  - Ford, 1925-2001, (5 folders) (Box 31)
  - Franklin, 1917-1928 (Box 31)
  - General Motors Corporation, 1929-1956 (Box 32)
  - GMC Trucks, 1919-1974 (Box 32)
  - Haynes, 1923 (Box 32)
  - Hudson, 1919-1956 (Box 32)
  - Hupmobile, 1919-1930 (Box 32)
  - Hyundai, 2000 (Box 32)
  - International Harvester (International Trucks), 1919-1974 (Box 32)
  - Isuzu, 1986-2001 (Box 32)
  - Jaguar, 1957-1990 (Box 32)
  - Jeep, 1946-2001 (Box 32)
  - Jordan, 1919-1920s (Box 32)
  - Kaiser-Frazer (includes Henry J.), 1948-1954 (Box 32)
  - Kissel Kar, 1915 (Box 32)
  - LaSalle, 1929 (Box 32)
  - Liberty, 1920 (Box 32)
  - Lincoln, 1930-1978, (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Locomobile, 1914 (Box 32)
  - Mack, 1958 (Box 33)
  - Marmon, 1912-1932 (Box 33)
  - Marquette, 1930 (Box 33)
  - Maxwell, 1919 (Box 33)
  - Mazda, 1998-2000 (Box 33)
  - Mercedes-Benz, 1961-1990 (Box 33)
  - Mercury, 1939-2002, (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - MG, 1962-1980 (Box 33)
  - Mitsubishi, 1988 (Box 33)
  - Morris, 1959-1960 (Box 33)
  - Nash, 1923-1958 (Box 33)
  - Oakland, 1917-1930 (Box 33)
  - Ohio Electric, 1913-1914 (Box 33)
  - Oldsmobile, 1922-2003, (5 folders) (Box 33)
  - Opel, 1959-1988 (Box 33)
  - Packard, 1906-1958, (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Paige, 1920-1927 (Box 34)
  - Peerless, 1914 (Box 34)
  - Peugeot, 1970-1988, (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Pierce (includes Arrow), 1912 (Box 34)
  - Plymouth, 1931-1995, (5 folders) (Box 34)
  - Pontiac, 1927-2000, (4 folders) (Box 34)
  - Porsche, 1963-1997 (Box 34)
  - Rambler/Hudson, 1955-1965 (Box 35)
  - Renault, 1956-1988, (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - Reo, 1912-1951, (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - Saab, 1960-1991 (Box 35)
  - Saturn, 1998-1999 (Box 35)
  - Saxon, 1914 (Box 35)
  - Sayers Six, 1919 (Box 35)
  - Simca, 1959-1967 (Box 35)
  - Stevens-Duryea, 1913 (Box 35)
  - Stewart, 1920 (Box 35)
  - Studebaker, 1910-1960, (3 folders) (Box 35)
  - Stutz, 1922-1926 (Box 35)
  - Subaru, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Suzuki, 1980-1999 (Box 35)
  - Thomas Flyer, 1909 (Box 35)
  - Toyota, 1964-2000 (Box 35)
  - Triumph, 1958 (Box 35)
  - Volkswagen, 1959-2000 (Box 35)
  - Volvo, 1962-1986 (Box 35)
  - White, 1912-1929 (Box 35)
  - Willis-Knight (includes Jeep and Overland), 1914-1955 (Box 35)
- Norman Rockwell Collection, 1924-1974, (1 box)
  Includes illustrations and print advertisements featuring artwork by Norman Rockwell. Advertisements include Crest toothpaste, Green Giant, Kellogg's, Massachusetts Mutual, Plymouth, Sharon Steel, Swiss watches, and Upjohn; covers for Saturday Evening Post, and artwork for Savings Bonds and other public service campaigns.
  - Print advertisements and illustrations (Box 36)
- N.W. Ayer & Sons Materials, 1894-1994 and undated, (3 boxes)
  Includes print advertisements, commercial reels and printed materials that document some of the advertising work performed by the N.W. Ayer & Son agency. Arranged by format.
  - DuPont Teflon Commercials
    Restrictions on Access: Original audiovisual materials are closed to research until use copies can be produced. Contact Research Services for more information.
    - DuPont Co. Commercials (Box 37)
      - 1. 68-5545. Ralph Coverwell. 16mm color. Undated. TRT: 45 sec. (Box 37)
      - 2. Unnumbered. Stella Spatterly. 16mm. Undated. TRT: 60 sec. (Box 37)
      - 3. 68-5667. Tom N.--Hunt Film Service--Rocky. 16mm color. 1968. TRT: 20 sec. (Box 37)
      - 4. DDGT-8043. DuPont Silverstone Spells Durability. 16mm. Undated. TRT: 30 sec. (Box 37)
    - DuPont TV Commercials (Box 37)
      [16mm. Includes DDFT0009 Scrambled Eggs 60 sec.; DDFT0008 Winner 60 sec.; 68-5760 German Food 30 sec.; 68-5760 Bake Ware 30 sec.; 68-5761 After a Great Meal 30 sec.]
    - Teflon Dealer Reel with Announcer Inserts, undated (Box 37)
  - Printed Material, 1949-1994
    - 125 Years of Building Brands, N.W. Ayer publication, 1994 (Box 38)
    - History of an Advertising Agency, Ralph Hower, Harvard University Press, 1949 (Box 38)
    - In Behalf of Management, N.W. Ayer & Son, 1949 (Box 38)
    - Washington Square, N.W. Ayer & Son, 1957 (Box 38)
- Roy Lightner Files, 1982-1984 and undated, (1 box)
  - Ernest P. Worrell Vern campaigns local publicity (Carden & Cherry Advertising), 1982-1984 (Box 38)
  - Lightner clippings and miscellaneous, undated (Box 38)
  - N.W. Ayer metal plaque, undated (Box 37)
- Oversize Materials, (1 box)
  Includes large-format materials removed from other series and housed separately.
  - General Products and Services
    - Bendix, 1937 (Box 39)
    - Coca-Cola, 1970, 1986 (Box 39)
    - Del Monte, 1942 (Box 39)
    - Du Pont, 1969-1970 (Box 39)
    - Goodyear, 1945-1966 (Box 39)
    - Metropolitan Life (Peanuts), 1993 (Box 39)
    - Shell Oil, 1937 (Box 39)
    - TV Guide, 1961 (Box 39)
    - United States Steel, 1937 (Box 39)
  - Cars and Trucks
    - Buick, 1955 (Box 39)
    - Cadillac, 1961-1968 (Box 39)
    - Chevrolet, 1962-1976 (Box 39)
    - Chrysler, 1948 (Box 39)
    - International Scout, 1961 (Box 39)
    - Lincoln, 1954, 1960 (Box 39)
    - Pierce Arrow, 1930 (Box 39)
    - Pontiac, 1955-1961 (Box 39)
    - Toyota, 1999 (Box 39)
    - Willys-Overland, 1915 (Box 39)
    - Newspaper advertisements
      - Cadillac, 1986 (Box 39)
      - Chrysler, 1992 (Box 39)
      - Ford, 2001 (Box 39)
      - Jeep, 1986 (Box 39)
      - Volkswagen, 1998 (Box 39)